You can't manufacture America The silence was pitiful that day
A love is getting too cynical Passion's just physical these days
You analyze every one you meet But get no sign, loving eyes
Every night you admit defeat And cry yourself blind
If you can't wake up in the morning Cause your bed lies weakened at night
If you're lost, hurt, tired or lonely Can't control it, try as you might
May I find that love that won't leave you May I find it by the end of the day
You won't be lost, hurt, tired or lonely Something beautiful will come your way
The DJ said on the radio Life should be stereo each day
You prepare to cast the unsuitable State of some kind of beautiful
You just couldn't wait All your friends think you're satisfied
But they can't see your soul No, no, no
You forgot the time feeling petrified When they left alone
If you can't wake up in the morning Cause your bed lies weakened at night
If you're lost, hurt, tired or lonely Can't control it, try as you might
May I find that love that won't leave you May I find it by the end of the day
You won't be lost, hurt, tired or lonely Something beautiful will come your way
Some kind of beautiful Some kind of beautiful
Some kind of beautiful All your friends think you're satisfied
But they can't see your soul No, no, no
You forgot the time feeling petrified When they left alone
If you can't wake up in the morning Cause your bed lies weakened at night
If you're lost, hurt, tired or lonely Can't control it, try as you might
May I find that love that won't leave you May I find it by the end of the day
You won't be lost, hurt, tired or lonely Something beautiful will come your way